<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://blog.giglab.io</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.giglab.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 23:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 23:49:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>

    
    
    <item>
      <title>September Update</title>
      <link>http://blog.giglab.io/2014/09/30/update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author></author>
      <guid>http://blog.giglab.io/2014/09/30/update</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The GigLab is pretty late into its Mozilla Gigabit Community Fund pilot period, and from the outside looking in we don’t have a lot to show for it. But developing a space like this has a lot of moving parts! I’m writing this to the tune of clanking pipes and grinding steel as electricians upgrade the 4th Floor’s electricity to support the added load of The GigLab*. This ensures both The 4th Floor and The GigLab have room to grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve been dealing with multiple vendors and funding sources, including most recently The Tennessee State Library and Archives, to fill The GigLab with amazing gig-enabled equipment. Check out our &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.giglab.io/resources&quot;&gt;resources list&lt;/a&gt; to see the resources we’re going to be offering. That should be enough to get you excited about our launch event on November 8th! We’ll post more details about this as they become available, but until then keep an eye on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/giglabcha&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; for more frequent updates. Also, feel free to come see our demo at the Creative Discovery Museum on Thursday, October the 9th from 5:30 to 7:30. This is a free admissions day, and many other amazing Gigabit Community Fund projects will also be in attendance. Hope to see you there!
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/post2.JPG&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is The GigLab?</title>
      <link>http://blog.giglab.io/2014/09/13/begin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author></author>
      <guid>http://blog.giglab.io/2014/09/13/begin</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Chattanooga Public Library has had access to gigabit speed internet since 2012. The 4th Floor is &lt;a href=&quot;http://chattlibrary.org/content/inclusive-gigabit-libraries&quot;&gt;“bathed in connectivity”&lt;/a&gt; to use the words of Nate Hill, the library’s deputy director. The GigLab builds on top of this bandwidth ubiquity in a way that provides a separate but inclusive gig-connected space designed specifically for gigabit-related experimentation and learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll do this by offering access to enterprise-level &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.giglab.io/resources&quot;&gt;gigabit connected hardware&lt;/a&gt; to the general public, as well as a variety of short-session and hands on courses regarding networking as a whole, and all things gigabit focused. We’re going to post a full list of courses we’re developing soon, so follow us on Twitter! And please feel free to submit your own ideas!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We view the gig as one of the 21st century’s most inspiring and potential-filled platforms for innovation and collaboration. We hope the GigLab serves as a catalyst for this platform’s continued development, and the general public’s continued learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We plan to officially launch the GigLab as a publicly accessible space in early November. But if you’re interested in signing up to lead a session or volunteering to help set the place up, &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1qU8K7jnsD6kkoX0X7lZXtUC90iVvtWDWdYQ-uM4ZrUs/viewform?usp=send_form&quot;&gt;we’d love to hear from you&lt;/a&gt;. In the mean time, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/giglabcha&quot;&gt;follow us on Twitter&lt;/a&gt; for frequent updates about setup and the latest gig-related developments.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/post1.JPG&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    

  </channel> 
</rss>